New Girl. New School. New Rules.
Wild Child is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Nick Moore.
Sixteen-year-old Poppy has everything her unlimited credit
cards can buy, and a spoiled attitude to match.
After a final thoughtless prank, her exasperated father
ships her off to boarding school in England.
There, Poppy meets her match in a stern headmistress and a class
full of girls who will not tolerate her selfishness.
Poppy Moore, played by Emma Roberts.
Freddie Kingsley, played by Alex Pettyfer.
Mrs. Kingsley, played by Natasha Richardson.
Kate, played by Kimberley Nixon.
Jennifer 'Drippy' Logan, played by Juno Temple.
Roddy, played by Johnny Pacar.
Wild Child is a 2008 teen comedy film directed by Nick Moore, written by Lucy Dahl, and starring Emma Roberts, Natasha Richardson, Shirley
Henderson, Alex Pettyfer and Aidan Quinn, with Georgia King, Kimberley Nixon, Juno Temple, Linzey Cocker and Sophie Wu.
Poppy Moore is a wealthy and spoiled American girl who is sent to a boarding school in England by her widowed father so that she is out of the way
long enough for him to carry out a series of overcomplicated bank heists, where she soon learns the true meaning of life and friendship.
This was Richardson's final film role before her death the following year.
Since its initial release, the film has gained a substantial cult following,
being particularly popular in the UK where the film is set.
The film explores themes of diving, england, boarding
school, girls' boarding school, malibu.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.